Hey, it's Celine Knox! Come with me to the Amphifestival this weekend.
First stop today, the ship!
I think it's going to take a while
We'll see you next time.
Thank you.
She played a perfect love scene
Pretty girl of sweet sixteen
Shiny glitter in her blue eyes
Not a girl a man would despise
She costed me a great stare
My little private puppeteer
Perfect silky white and soft skin
A seductive but forbidden sin
So first day of the Amphifestival today.
It is really hot.
I'm wearing this. It's still hot and I'm going to see some awesome bands today.
I wanted to see Empathy Test but the venue was full. I didn't get inside. Bummer.
Sitting at the Beach Club here which is really fun because you have a lot of
people here with black clothes and the wide beach. So always fun and it's always
cool to sit here and have a drink in the evening and enjoy the beautiful weather
at the ride.
So good, 16 months up and cold And I knew I should, should get a hold of myself
So where are you from?
I'm from Belgium
From Belgium? It's your first time up here?
No, it's the third time with the stand but I think we've been here already like 7 or 10 times
Oh wow, so you love the scene, you love the girl's scene
Yes, I love it
And what do you think of the corset?
It looks amazing on you.
It's like completely the right size and you handle it well.
Do you make major measure corsets?
Yeah, I have my examples in the store,
but I cannot make every single measure or fabric you like.
End of the first day here at Amphi Festival in Cologne and I'm still sweating because it was so hot
it's going to be even hotter tomorrow oh my god my feet are hurting because I
danced so much but I had a lot of fun especially for the last band, the
Invinination, the crowd was so amazing and the venue was full I love this venue
the Tanzbom and also the bands had so much fun so it was an awesome day and I'm
looking forward to tomorrow. Second day of the festival I tried to press
according to the weather because it's super hot again. I don't want to see as
much bands as yesterday so I have more time to go shopping.
I tried to taste like I'm blind
But it's still so hard to ignore those tears
I just bought the corset I tried on yesterday.
Oh, it's so cool.
I'm so happy and I'm still sweating.
Everyone is seeking the shadow and shades.
Two more bands I'll see today and I hope it's going to be a bit colder.
We're going to head inside to see Lauren after midnight and I hope you had fun with this
video.
See you maybe at Amphi next year.
Bye!
In this time went by I hurt less and less with myself
The cold winds all around
Just becomes a storm and I'm lying still
And I don't really care what will remain
Of life and you and me
I turn over the pages to a blank
But how could I assuage the fire in my head?
I don't want the answers to be burnt
I never ask for reasons in the end
you